window2india.com 2007-05-19

# window2india

Protecting your privacy is very important to us. We want you to fully understand our privacy practices and therefore, we have created Window2india Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review this policy carefully before you access our services.

How does Window2india Shopping protect your privacy?

To avail certain services on window2india.shopping Site, user/s are required to provide certain information for the registration process namely:- a) name including first and last name, b) email address and alternate email address , c) demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address and durables owned); d) mobile phone number and contact details, f) PIN code; e)preferences and interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on) etc., and / or your occupation, interests, and the like. (All required information is Service Dependent). However, TOML may also collect the following information:

  * about the pages you visit/access
  * the links you click on our site
  * the number of times you access the page.

If your personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), or if you no longer desire our product(s)/service(s), you shall correct or update your personal data. 

Window2india Shopping will not give out your telephone number or e-mail address, except where needed to deliver a product or service you ordered. We will not give out your credit card number or any account information unless you authorize it, e.g., processing a credit card payment.

TOML do not rent or sell your name, address, email address, credit card information or personal information to any third party without your permission. This information is collected primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver you a truly personalized shopping experience. 

All information gathered on windows2india.com Site is securely stored within the TOML's controlled database. The database is stored on servers secured behind a firewall; access to the servers is password-protected and is strictly limited. However, as effective as our security measures are, no security system is impenetrable. TOML cannot guarantee the security of its database, nor can it guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to TOML over the Internet. And, of course, any information you include in a posting to the discussion areas is available to anyone with Internet access However, TOML will not use your financial information for any purpose other than to complete a transaction with you.

Nonetheless, we must cooperate fully, should a situation arise, where we are required by law or statutory obligation or legal process to provide information about the user. We may share non-personal, non-individual statistical or demographic information, in aggregate form, with our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties for research and advertising purposes. In other words, we will not give out information that you purchased a specific product, but we may tell them how many customers purchased a product.

If you have purchased from our store or subscribed to one of our newsletters, we may occasionally update you via e-mail of special new product arrivals, features or schemes on our site. We may also contact you if you have participated in one or more of our contests. If you choose not to receive updates when you enter a contest, it will not affect your chances of winning the same. If you wish not to receive the newsletters, simply send us a message from our Feedback section choosing unsubscribe as the subject.

We may change our privacy policy from time to time to incorporate necessary future changes. Of course, our use of any information we gather will always be consistent with the policy under which the information was collected, regardless of what the new policy may be.

By visiting this Site you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.

By accepting the Window2india Privacy Policy and Window2india Terms & Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Window2india Terms & Conditions.
